clickandchat.com 2012-10-19

# Our Privacy Policy : Live Chat Application : Live Chat Software : ClickAndChat.com

### Privacy Policy

We are committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy details how we use your personal identifying information. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice to you. Please review this document each time you visit us or use any of our tools or services. Our Privacy Policy is our commitment to you that we provide not only the highest quality services and products, but that we understand that you expect us to safeguard the personal and business information that we collect. To this end, our Privacy Policy allows you to make an informed decision regarding your usage of the tools and services that we provide. As technology and circumstances change, we will continue to update, modify and enhance this Privacy Policy for your benefit as part of our commitment to you to provide the best possible services and security according to our high standards of business practices and ethics.

  By using the tools and services we provide, and visiting our web site such activities become your express indication to us that you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described herein. If we modify or enhance our Privacy Policies and related procedures, we will publish those modifications on this web page in order to make you aware of any such changes.

  **Confidentiality of Your Data**  
We will not share with any third party or entity the personal, business or corporate data or personal information that we collect. All such information shall be confidentially maintained by our company. We shall use such information strictly for the purpose of providing services to you, our user, and we will house such data and information strictly for the purpose of providing services for your benefit.

  **Exceptions to our Privacy Policy**  
Possible exceptions to our policy include the following circumstances, and as indicated herein:

  1. If a governmental agency, or an attorney, subpoenas your private information, or makes a formal request for discovery pursuant to any legal action, or pending legal action.
  2. If our attorneys request such information relevant to a current or pending legal matter in which you are a potential or actual party or otherwise contributed in some way to the causation of the legal matter.

**Special Considerations**  
In order to access certain subscriber services and restricted areas (the “Restricted Services”) within the ClickAndChat.com site (the “Site”), ClickAndChat.com requires that you provide certain identifying information (the “Registration Data”) listed in the online registration form. This information may include your legal name, address, telephone number(s), email address, subscriber name or “username,” password, method of payment, and, if applicable, credit card number. ClickAndChat.com reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account.

  **Confidentiality**  
Registration Data is the property of ClickAndChat.com, subject to and protected by the Electronic Communications Privacy Act. ClickAndChat.com will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose your Registration Data to any third party. ClickAndChat.com maintains a secured area on the Site for transmission of Registration Data, and stores all Registration Data in a private database which is not connected to the Internet.

  **Uses of Registration Data**  
Unless you elect to “Opt-Out” as described herein, ClickAndChat.com reserves the right to use your Registration Data to send you information about ClickAndChat.com, the Site, ClickAndChat.com products and services, and other topics in which you have indicated an interest.

  **Opt-Out Right**  
If you do not wish to receive any special offers or other communications from ClickAndChat.com, you have the right to “opt-out” by emailing [support@clickandchat.com](mailto:support@clickandchat.com).

  **Cookies**  
Please note that we may employ the use of cookies. Currently we may employ cookies when users create user accounts or register to use certain tools throughout our web site. But we may further employ cookies to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future.

  Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we may use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions.

  The information gathered is not shared with third parties. You may turn off your cookies by adjusting the appropriate settings on your browser. Please consult the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to adjust or turn your cookies off. Cookies do not reveal personal information and if you turn off your cookies you may find your enjoyment ease of use of the Internet, and our site, to be reduced or impaired.

  In order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use your email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes.

  Cookies may provide Recording Session information, show us visitor preferences regarding return visits to our web site, help us to manage subscription or private areas on our web site, record user specific tracking or aggregate tracking information of visitors and deliver user customized content based on user specific information, such as browser type, operating system type, operating system version number and so forth. None of the information gathered is shared with third parties.

  Other possible uses for the information that we collect includes internal tracking, review, or is used for contacting purposes and then is archived by us for future usage. We also use the information we collect to provide custom content for our user base. Technical and business statistics are also collected via cookies: which allows us to tract the various paths users trace through our web site as they move from one web page to another. Cookies also account for the number of users who visit our site and to calculate the visitor capacity and scalable architecture of our web site. We do not use cookie technology to gather personal information about you.

  Cookies are used as an important element of our ClickAndChat.com application to help us determine return users and to collect important user data and information which is useful to the user of the ClickAndChat.com application.

  **Links to Third Party Web Sites**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web Sites linked to or from our Web Site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web Sites are provided as a courtesy to you. Always review the Privacy Policies of such web sites.

  **General Information**  
It is our policy not to send unsolicited emails or allow third parties to contact you via the email address that you provide to us. We may, from time to time, contact you to discuss business relevant to your membership and, naturally, we will contact you to respond to inquiries that you may send to us.

  We do not collect information about our visitors from third party sources, such as public records or entities, or private organizations.

  We do not knowingly collect personal data or information from minors.

  We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control. These policies, rules and technical measures help to protect your data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. However, note that no policy, rule or technical measure can offer 100% protection against unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

  All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obligated to respect the confidentiality of our visitor’s and members’ personal data.

  We use your personal information, in a general sense, to operate our business; that means that we use the information to provide customer service and to provide tools and services to our user base, including, individually, you or your business. We may also use the information we collect for the purpose of alerting you about changes to our business, web site or special offers we think you will find to be important. All emails sent to you are done so pursuant to standard industry security approaches and standards. You will be given the opportunity, during every correspondence, to notify us that you desire not to receive special offers, however, we do reserve the right to communicate with your regarding any direct business or customer account concerns relevant to your account and of course, to respond to any inquiries or comments that you forward to us regarding your account of the activities of our business or any other use of our tools and services.

  Your password is protected by us from unauthorized access and usage via standard security approaches. However, no such process is 100% secured. Also, we advise you to never share your password and other sensitive information with any third party and to always verify by examining the address placed into your browser’s URL section that you are actually present at our web site before you enter in your user ID and password information.

  How Can You Access and Correct Your Information? You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing [support@clickandchat.com](mailto:support@clickandchat.com).

  Evaluation of our Privacy Policy practices and internal protocols; from time to time, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with internal policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. We provide ongoing training for regarding our standards and practices regarding the safeguarding of your personal information and in general limit access to any such information to those employees who are authorized to attend to your information for such reasonably required and necessary access thereto.

  **Credit Card Usage, Aggregated Data and More**  
We may collect aggregate (general tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site. We also may collect user specific information about pages that users visit on our site. Any information that you give us when you complete a contact form or inquiry form, survey and so forth is collected by us.

  Should you engage in a business transaction with us, such as purchasing a tool, product or service, we will collect the information necessary to complete that transaction. Credit card based purchases generally require you to provide the following information: your name, mailing address, email address, credit card number, home and or business phone number and other personal information, such as security codes or information such as your mother’s maiden name. We maintain your credit card related information once your purchase has been verified and processed via your credit card service provider for future usage, within a secured system. In the event of a charge back, the credit card service provider will provide us with such information for the purpose of our evaluation of the charge back request, including any protestations and or feedback issued by our company if we determine fraud has taken place. In the event of credit card fraud and similar defaulted payments, the credit card related information shall be used for collection related purposes.

  Credit card information sent to use via our web site is transferred and transmitted via secure server software that provides industry standard encryption. Other information that you send via standard email will not be subjected to this high level of encryption so we advise you accordingly that you should never submit sensitive personal information such as credit card numbers and so forth via standard email to us.

  **Lost or Stolen Information**  
If your credit card or password is stolen or used without your permission, immediately notify ClickAndChat. Upon notification ClickAndChat will cancel your credit card number and/or password and update its records. You may be unable to access certain services while ClickAndChat processes the credit card and/or password change.

  **Cancellation**  
You may cancel your account at any time by sending an email to [support@clickandchat.com](mailto:support@clickandchat.com). Once ClickAndChat has finished processing the cancellation, ClickAndChat will delete all your Registration Data from its database.

  Use of Aggregated Information. ClickAndChat reserves the right to disclose to third parties information about Subscriber usage of the ClickAndChat Web site and any related services, including information gathered during your use of the Site. Any information disclosed will be in the form of aggregate data (such as overall patterns or demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual user.

  **Communications**  
If you communicate with us, via email or telephone or even via surface mail, we will maintain such communications and the information contained within them for the purpose and providing customer services to you. We employ industry standard protections for all such communications.

  You may be required to complete online registration forms that provide us with contact information (such as your name and street address), your email address and your phone numbers.

  We may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our service so that we can directly communicate with you regarding issues we determine to be relevant.

  **No Liability for Acts of Third Parties**  
Although ClickAndChat will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the Registration Data, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. ClickAndChat will have no liability for disclosure of Registration Data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

  ClickAndChat reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other company policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the Site. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.

  **Contacting Us**

Web Technologies, Inc.  
ClickAndChat.com  
225 E Broadway Suite 214  
Glendale, CA 91205

(888) 456-1147

Last Updated 08/19/2011
